♪ In the not‐too‐distant
future ♪
♪ next Sunday a, d, ♪
♪ there was
a guy named Joel ♪
♪ not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ he worked
at gizmonic institute ♪
♪ just another face
in red jump suit ♪
♪ he did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ but his bosses
didn't like him ♪
♪ and they shot him
into space! ♪
♪ We'll send him
cheesy movies ♪
♪ the worst we can find ♪
♪ la! La! La! ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ then we'll monitor
his mind ♪
♪ la! La! La! ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ when the movies
begin and end ♪
♪ la! La! La! ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ to make his robot friends ♪
♪ robot roll call ♪
♪ cambot ♪
♪ gypsy ♪
♪ Tom servo ♪
♪ crow ♪
♪ if you're wondering
how he eats and breathes ♪
♪ and other science facts ♪
♪ la! La! La! ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself
its just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ for mystery science
theater ♪
♪ 3000 ♪
Hey, everybody,
my name is Joel,
I'm marooned up here
in outer space,
I'm all alone
except for the companionship
of my two robot friends
that are of my own design,
there are two evil
overlord scientists
that are sending me
horrendous films,
but I can handle it
because I'm a hu‐man,
two, three,,,
♪ [blues harmonica]
♪ Hey, there, you people
in front of your tvs ♪
♪ sitting along that line ♪
♪ I'll be back
from the commercial ♪
♪ in a few minutes time ♪
[Woman]
Commercial sign in five,
four, three, two,
commercial sign now‐‐
♪ ain't that a hu‐man ♪
♪ [Harmonica]
♪ H‐u‐m‐a‐n ♪
♪ a human, human ♪
Cheese it, you guys,
get rid of the harps,
it's the overlords,
good day, my muddy waters
wannabe,
good day, sirs,
how's everything on earth?
How would we know?
We've been subterranean
for 932 days
we're as abstracted
from reality as you are,
maybe more,
gee, don't say hi,
well, is it time for
the invention exchange?
Is it time
for the invention exchange?
Yes, show us what you've got,
pink boy,
well, you know how it is
on earth
when they have those giant,
enclosed stadiums
and you can't smoke in them,
and I always thought
it was kind of peculiar
because you can drive giant,
hell belching monster trucks
but you can't smoke, right?
‐ yeah, yeah, right,
‐ yeah, yeah,
so I invented this thing,
it's a thing for smokers,
and it's a monster truck,
I call it the nitro‐burning
funny pipe,
and I just start it up here,
okay?
And then I light a match here,
ow,
[imitating monster truck ads]
Sunday, Sunday, Sunday,
we'll see Joel's lung
turn into a giant tar pit,
wow, that's real,
gear‐crushing,
tire popping
tobacco satisfaction,
oh, yes, very nice,
although we don't smoke,
well, here's ours, joeliase,
as you know,
face masks throughout history
left the bank robber, or thug,
completely expressionless,
well, we've taken care of that,
Larry,
we've invented the stocking
mask of the future,
with articulated eyebrows,
yes, no longer will
a desperate criminal
go misunderstood,
the s‐m of f takes care
of that completely,
uh, the demo, Larry,
all right,
put $10,000 in the bag,
unmarked bills right now,
hey, ladies,
it works, cool,
all right, see, you touch
that alarm button
and I'm going to have
to rip off your fingers,
and you're going to have
to reattach at the nearest
hospital
with laser surgery,
it's really cool
how they do that,
‐ Larry,
‐ sorry,
see, I know
what you're thinking,
you're thinking, did I use six
bullets or only five,
see, in all the excitement,
I don't know myself,
I saw it in a movie,
it's really gr‐‐
Clint and‐‐
yes, well, that's our
experiment this week, Joel,
now, the movie is
a greasy little sci‐fi number
called robot holocaust,
and it's in color,
yay!
But it's edited
for television,
boo,
fruits you must never enjoy,
joelene,
but there's more,
I know, commando Cody, right?
Exactly,
deal with it, smart boy,
enjoy,
‐ [alarm buzzing]
‐ clamoring
[Joel] You know what?
I was saying they
use servos to move
those eyebrows,
[Tom servo]
Sunday, Sunday, Sunday,
‐ yours is cool, Joel,
‐ thanks,
hey, is that his high school
yearbook picture?
Hm, I don't know,
there's a bunch of rocks ahead
that'll give us some shelter,
it's heading for some rocks,
we'll have to stop,
[Joel]
They must've read the script,
That's our feed pressure line,
we're stuck,
I'll say we are,
pressure's down to nothing,
‐ I could fix this
if I have time,
‐ and if I know how,
I could try to stop it
with your grenades,
okay,
‐ it's got behind a rock,
‐ which one of us is talking?
I think I can blast him,
right at the plywood,
now I'm just going to drop
my spleen on him,
what was that?
Sounded like a spleen,
by this time my lungs
were aching for air,
If the tank's a rockin',
don't come a knockin',
huh?
Oh, great, he's drunk again
on rye whisky,
‐ we're stuck,
‐ so is the other car,
let's go after them
with our a‐pistols,
Whoa, he's got
the zactlies big time,
did you stop them?
For a little while, but
I don't know for how long,
dude, I can't keep covering
for you at the office,
Guys, over here,
whoa,
taste my steel, jug head,
yikes,
that's not fair
to play catch like that,
oh, for the love of Mike,
‐ hess,
‐ come in here
and quit horsing around,
come on, mom,
just one more grenade,
little lead sandwich
for you, moon geek,
No, d for drive, Ted,
shrapnel on your brain?
♪ Jimmy crack corn,
and I don't care ♪
♪ my master's gone away ♪
Those things shut off quick,
yeah, you don't get run on
on the moon,
well, except for this movie,
which runs on and on,
true,
Ted, we can't bring
your puppet everywhere,
Jimmy likes to travel, Cody,
‐ I'll ditch this car,
‐ right,
where you going to ditch
a high gloss plywood
moon vehicle?
Besides we don't call them
ditches on the moon,
we call them craters,
hm, peaceful,
meanwhile,
back at the slagheap,
‐ okay, we're ready,
‐ right,
ready for what?
Are you going to let me go
before you leave?
No, we're taking you
with us,
and you better go back to your
quarters until we get started,
get going!
Take off that stupid hat,
Cody, don't wear your jet pack
in the house,
what if that thing went off?
Safety belts fastened?
They haven't been
invented yet, though,
‐ cool,
‐ moon man flambé,
Ron Howard pops the clutch
and tells the moon
to eat my dust,
What happened?
Hey,
film broke?
‐ hey,
‐ oh,
[groaning]
I'm going to go back
and check,
boo,
‐ let's see here,
‐ hey,
is it can bot, Joel?
I don't know,
I can't tell,
Hey, you guys,
I think I got it going,
cool,
yeah, it's working great,
it really is in color, too,
look,
just in time,
the last city still stood,
the remaining home
of what was left
of the civilization
of new terra,
Pittsburgh,
the society had been
all but destroyed
by the robot rebellion of '33,
oh, my hip still hurts
from that one,
cyborg blindsided me,
hey, look,
it's Aaron spelling's house,
boy, that place sure
isn't up to code,
it's three rivers stadium,
soon chaos had led
to a radiation spell,
far more deadly
than any nuclear warfare,
they barbecued in parks
with strict fire codes,
the world had been brought
to its knees
by the robot holocaust,
by the title,
Robert culf's smarter brother,
Nadine hart
of Rodgers and hart,
look at me, I'm a turtle,
is that you, Joel?
No, that's the other Joel,
there's two of us,
Jennifer delora,
she's a delorean,
Andrew howarth,
fine, howarth you?
‐ that's a good one,
‐ ba‐bing,
angelika jager,
she's playing
the big‐lipped woman,
Barry Flynn,
[Chortles]
Hello there,
Cynthia depaul,
good school,
great basketball team,
Tim Kincaid,
Reuben Kincaid's
smarter brother,
A parking ramp in Cincinnati,
I think it looks more
like a rollercoaster,
like six flags
over armageddon,
armageddon
tired of this already,
I bet those guys are fighting
over the last corndog
in existence,
Ooh, what happened to his butt?
Isn't there a salve for that?
You got a little something
on your mouth there,
wipe that,
ick,
get up, get up,
that's good,
you gotta want it,
I hate fights,
they're so smokey and noisy,
I'm editing this,
hm, inspected by number 12,
hey, couldn't he get arrested
for pulling that tag off?
Only if he was wearing
a mattress,
ah,
Looks like the sad future
of the wwf,
look at this robo pick pocket,
nice tag,
the remaining citizens
in newtown
are known as airslaves,
as far as they know,
the only other inhabitants
of the planet remain‐‐
help me,
,,,the evil being controls
the very atmosphere
that sustains them,
because as we all know,
to air is human,,,
,,,stories of nomads
who roam the wastelands
beyond the outskirts
of the city,
outlaws, loners,
a legendary breed
who have somehow acclimated
to the poisonous air,
actors, lawyers,
hot dog venders,
oh, god, I need this job,
hey, am I my resume?
Where's Bobby heenan
when you need him?
Wonder what would've happened
if there was card chairs
after the apocalypse,
if you wish to be
reactivated,
you will tell me
what takes place below,
below what?
I will give you a five second
activation to respond,
please, master,
I am sorry for trying to‐‐
why the long face?
,,,i am at your service,
you have three seconds,
a contest, master,
they're ventriloquisting
each other,
a fight to the death,
each month the dark one
sends a transbot
to each work encampment
in the city
to pick the
two strongest air slaves
against one another,
the dark one?
The ruler of all air slaves,
arsenio?
Their labor fuels
the power station,
the station cleanses
the atmosphere,
so that the workers
can continue
to fuel the power station,
and you?
I am but a poor freebot,
master,
‐ freebot,
‐ ooh, ooh,
,,,my only source of revenue,
I steal what I can
from who I can
in order to pay
for the upkeep
of my mechanical parts,
mechanical pot?
Is that a drug reference?
I don't think so,
you know, this movie's
no rocky, you guys,
thank goodness,
what is the reason
for these contests?
The true most powerful slaves
must fight
until one of them dies,
or until they capture
the other's loin cloth,
,,,to the power station
for his reward,
but it is said that the winner
is actually destroyed,
destroyed?
Yes, destroyed,
read my lips,
or lip,
this way the dark one
can keep the air slaves
from developing leaders
strong enough to lead
a rebellion,
the power station,
looks like they patched into
a metallica video, you guys,
think it's the maid,
what a maid it is,
something's wrong,
I can sense it,
must be cold in that room,
is this the amphitheater?
Yes, dark one,
did she say "stuffed one?"
I'm going to die if they start
dancing cheek to cheek
all of a sudden,
do the dirty bump,
look at that,
looks like sneeze stalactites,
[people chanting]
Nowhere! Nowhere!
I feel like I could get
into the middle of this soon,,,
take them, Joe,
kill, kill,
no, he's our brother,
he ain't heavy,
kill him,
huh?
Stop it,
this is no contest,
it is murder,
[laser zaps]
Well her corns are gone,
hey, it's miles Davis,
well, it's good to have goals,
little crab guy,
,,,weapons,
we can get them,
[crowd chanting]
What are they saying,
no winter?
Uh, no dinner, I think,
I don't think they want
Edgar winter to play,
‐ no acting, no acting,
‐ no, Jonathan winter,
no winner! No winner!
Tehran, 1979,
No winner! No winner!
Peas and carrots,
peas and carrots,
no liver?
Valaria,
yes, doc one?
What did she say,
"stock one"?
Lock John?
Ooh, sore throat pain,
is that George Bush?
Pretend you're
like the others,
‐ father,
‐ do as I say,
fall down,
try to look realistic,
very nice,
who stands against
the forces of
the power station?
Restore the atmosphere,
and I will identify myself,
look out, he's got
an eggplant,
restore the atmosphere,
very well,
you dare to test the power
of my dreaded eggplant?
Oh, my aching crowd scene,
everybody, up, up, crowd,
did you all
have to be reminded
who is in control,
and what happens when
the dark one is disobeyed?
‐ pork one?
‐ all but one,
he will be attended to,
but for the moment,
torque, destroy
the fighters,
oh, what a waste
of an extra,
oh,
you hate to see them
go like that,
take refuge in the crowd
and save yourself,
‐ no, my place is with you,
‐ oh, we'd better get going,
I'm willing to be here
to protect you, do it!
‐ carry me,
‐ no, walk yourself,
it is you who
need protection,
deeja, now,
Picking through the n‐‐
stop, human, you have
entered the we zone,
a world that revolves
around us and only us,
all right, well, I was
just going to the galley
to get some food,
you know, and‐‐
what do you want?
No one crosses
the we zone without
doing something
for us first,
okay, what do
you want me to do?
You must do
the disappearing coin trick,
‐ yeah, good idea,
‐ all right,
I can do that for you,
remember how it goes, right?
Start with
an ordinary quarter,
all right, and then I start
rubbing it on my elbow
like that,
see that, cambot?
Okay, and‐‐ oops,
I didn't get it
to disappear yet,
let's try it again,
I take the quarter,
and rub it, and it's gone,
‐ hey, cool,
‐ okay, can I go now?
Now, you must, uh,
walk us on the ceiling,
no, crow, in character,
you must walk us
on the ceiling,
you guys‐‐ you guys know
you're getting
way too big for that,
I can't walk you
on the ceiling,
what else you want me to do?
Mm, you must create
a severe weather condition
inside the satellite,
‐ yeah,
‐ like what?
You know,
the Chinese snow trick,
oh, I can't do
snowstorm in China,
it's in the shop,
I'd have to go get it,
what can I do
that's real quick?
Uh, do goofus face for us,
yeah, crazy duck face,
okay, I'll do it,
[servo laughs]
Ugh! Not the eyelids, ew,
‐ I hate that,
‐ all right, can I go now?
Uh, no, you must,,,
‐ do for us a handstand,
‐ yeah,
okay, if I do a handstand,
can I go then?
‐ oh, of course,
‐ all right, all right,
let's try it here,
all right, ready?
Handstand on
the count of three,
three, two, one,
and up!
Oh cool,
how's that, you guys?
‐ shoes untied,
‐ okay,
and down,
great,
all right, I'm gonna
go to the galley now,
you guys want anything?
Yes, human, well,
now that you mention it,
ravioli would be nice,
yeah, and I'd like
a club sandwich,
oh, and could you pull the extra
bread out of the middle?
‐ I hate that,
‐ okay, no problem,
I'll see you around,
I love dinner theater,
yeah, you know it, pal,
And now, man,
who are you?
I am but a simple man,
dark one,
a man who is clearly
no match for your powers,
and yet, you breathe
the poisoned air,
I have no explanation,
perhaps a visit
to the power station
will loosen your tongue,
torque, take him,
And no dinner,
Hey, she didn't say anything,
who are you to keep me
from my father?
Dave,
his name is Neo,
he comes from the wastelands
beyond the city,
you are immune
to the poison air?
He can live anywhere
on new terra,
why must we listen to a freebot
instead of the man himself?
He speaks to me
telepathically,
actually, it's more
tele‐pathetically,
‐‐you will side with him,
if he aims to defeat
the dark one,
we stand with him,
‐ hmm,
‐ and you,
my father is in danger,
what do you want of me?
Just five minutes
of your time,
you know, I know
you haven't really
considered aluminum siding,
‐‐not affected,
my father is a scientist,
‐ huh?
‐ he has created
a small device
which subverts
the dark one's
atmosphere control,
he only had time to create
one for himself and me
before he was taken away,
they're real expensive,
oh, she's wearing
a beltone,
ew, cooties,
these workyards used
to have something called
subway system,
they used to be in things
called "ci‐ties,"
‐‐set up his shop
in one of these rooms,
now that the device
has been perfected,
he said that we could all
be fitted for one
within the next few days,
they would work
in the wastelands as well?
[All] Shut up,
‐‐been sent here
by the rebel society
from what you call
the wastelands,
we are organizing an army
to destroy the dark one
and his forces
at the power station,
if you swear
your allegiance to Neo,
hey, it's a young
Robin Williams
on the right there,
right there,
‐‐and rescue your scientist,
so your,,,
tribe is some kind
of hybrid race?
Yeah, you could say that,
you could say that,
our number grows each day,
thanks to me,
now that you know
of my father's device,
you need us as much
as we need you,
‐ and vice‐versa,
‐ we don't need
the device,
you do,
but an army of airslaves
who are no longer
really airslaves‐‐
I can't believe they
cut away to me again,
get the camera off me,
I am looking for a friend,
the odds aren't too good,
‐‐power station,
together we will go there,
and regain control
of the last city
and new terra,
[narrator] And so, the new
band of rebels set out‐‐
who is that guy?
They started at a landfill
outside Manhattan,
‐‐wastelands,
♪ Take my hand ♪
I'm a stranger in paradise,
I guess it's a wasteland
if you don't count
that big city behind you,
go to the u, n, building,
it's filled with people,
behind you!
Maybe they're looking for
the renaissance festival,
and over here, we did
"Shakespeare in the slagheap,"
it was very nice,
follow the yellow brick road,
strange mutants live
in the wastelands,
‐ posing a threat to‐‐
‐ the shrubbery is alive,
they finally found
the path again,
if I was skeptical,
I'd say
that was central park,
Hey, look at this,
it says, "this is not
a men's room,"
I think it says,
"no graphics,"
look, it's the bangles,
no, it's the road show
of "cats,"
eh, they're at
the winter garden,
I'll be back
again and again,
Ah, here's my Mark,
‐ here's mine,
‐ hey, that's my Mark,
and I'm here,
everybody stare on camera,
don't go for your weapons,
who is this woman who walks
through the she‐zone
with male scum?
The woman is with us,
I speak to the woman,
I walk with these men
on a mission
to save my father,
‐ is that Wendy or Lisa?
‐ another man?
Have you no principles?
I love my father,
he's made a promise
to save him,
no man is to be trusted,
then how can
your tribe survive?
We use men
to breed with us
to create
future warrior women,
‐ cool,
‐ then we dispose of them,
‐ oh,
‐ look,
‐ he is the last man‐‐
‐ hey!
‐ who ventured into
our territory,
‐ it's great!
He has mated
with all of us
who are ready to conceive,
and he will
now be destroyed,
and he has nothing
to say about this?
I think he'd
highly recommend it,
‐‐when we find one of you
is to remove your tongue,
men chatter so,
you cowardly bitch,
I would stop if I were you,
why? What difference
would the life
of one puny man make?
Perhaps none,
but there's a laser
pointed at your head,
[all] Huh?
How do I know
you're not lying?
There's only one way
to find out, isn't there?
What do you want?
A chance for a fair fight,
[narrator] A knife
is placed in the ground,
a voice‐over is placed
in the script,
they're gonna play
mumblety‐peg?
I'm gonna cut you, man,
I'm gonna cut you real good,
tear him apart!
You know,
the more things change,
the more they stay the same,
you know, like the way
guys and gals get together
and just love,
central park hasn't
really changed either,
rip his flesh!
David Lee roth!
Emmett Kelly,
puny man, eh?
By the rules of our tribe,
I belong to you to do
what you will with me,
‐ all right!
‐ what do you suggest?
Kill me,
because if I get the chance,
I will kill you,
and why should I kill you?
Your people are
like me, aren't they?
Look at that,
she's stuffing kleenex,
you can breathe the air,
‐ the dark one?
‐ what a time to get a cold,
we don't fear him,
he sends transbots
to tame us,
and we cut them into scrap,
your ancestors came
from the wasteland,
we have no history,
we have always been here,
so you have a history,
‐‐who can exist here
without the device,
only Nyla's women,
we had heard
stories of them,
you can help lead us
to the power station,
I know where it is,
then you will
take us to it,
‐ maybe,
‐ if that is your desire,
but once my debt
to you is paid,
I will kill you,
if you live that long,
threats, threats,
threats,
you will come with us,
Kai, what do you
say to us?
‐ hello,
‐ maybe none,
sometimes people
can be helped
for no reason other than
human charity,
and he can sign,
‐‐they're all useless
and crazy,
[servo coughs]
I think I have
this calendar,
deep in the power station
lies the pleasure machine,
‐ all right!
‐ a reward
to those who loyally serve
the dark one,
What?
‐ valaria!
‐ dark one, i‐‐
the pleasure machine
is to be used
as a reward, not a habit,
yes, dark one,
it would serve you well‐‐
dark one, [mumbles],
‐ i‐‐
‐ the discussion is ended,
there are other matters
to attend to,
pretty self‐indulgent
for someone
with a speech impediment,
torque, my guard dogs
bring you a new subject
for interrogation,
yes, dark one,
is she wearing a kitchen mat?
Yeah, she'd better not go out
in the sun in that outfit,
torque, have the man
freed from his bonds,
James Bond,
there is no reason
for him to be,,,
uncomfortable,
but I kind of
like the chains,
you know,
you look familiar,
were you in
yards of leather?
There, isn't that better?
What, your accent?
It will benefit all of us
if you cooperate,
do you understand?
No, none of us understand,
we don't know
what you're saying,
you are impervious
to our atmosphere control,
hey, watch who you call
impervious, lady,
your stay with us could
be quite pleasant
if you choose
to work with us,
you mean you'll
stop talking?
On the other hand,
I could introduce you
to worlds of pain
beyond your imagination,
well, let's just skip
to the worlds of pain, then,
the choice is yours,
I have no answers for you,
a pity,
I am losing
Patience, valaria,
torque, take him
to the crystal,
torque? Oh, that's what
happened to Peter tork,
he's doing
rubber suit work now,
after the monkees broke up,
‐ that's interesting,
‐ I knew that haircut
would come back,
at the crystal,
jorn can see
that the dark one
is aware of the rebels‐‐
there's that guy again,
she's your daughter,
isn't she?
‐ maybe,
‐ let go of me,
muslin face,
it would be a pity
if she had to lose her life
because of your silence,
I have nothing to say,
uh, except for
what I just said,
my daughter would
want it that way,
then your daughter
is a bigger fool
than you are,
she could just, like,
clear her throat or something,
torque, take him to
the room of questions,
where is the room
of questions?
Would you stop that?
Don't even start,
hey, wait for me,
we will see just how long
he can keep
his secrets to himself,
your work is cut out
for you, valaria,
‐ your dress is
cut out for you,
‐ yes, dark one,
‐ "stock watt"?
‐ "stock worm"?
Yes, dark one,
‐ stock wan,
‐ duck bun, I think,
beats me,
see how we've used
this ground cover
to halt the erosion
on this hill?
There,
what is it?
‐ the caverns start here,
‐ caverns?
Yes, caverns, like
what's in your ear,
‐‐connects to the power station
from underground,
the dark one has ways
of monitoring our progress
if we continue
on the surface,
come,
I hate when he does that,
[narrator] The mutants
continued to follow the rebels
even as they entered
the underground caverns,
hey, it's shelley Duvall,
We must be quiet
from here on in,
‐ why?
‐ writers' strike,
‐ sewage worms,
‐ same thing,
sewage worms,
man‐eating creatures
from the‐‐
they look like
pink socks
with teeth in them,
humans,
they eat humans,
how about a show of hands?
This is their nest,
if we can get
to the other side,
we'll be safe,
safe? We'll never
make it through,
what kind of
a woman are you?
Have you no fighting spirit?
Enough,
let's see
how many there are,
he's carrying
a giant beef stick,
it's kukla!
How can we
make it through?
If only we had some kind
of bait to distract them
while the rest of us
slipped through,
bait, sock bait?
‐‐will surely be attacked
by the worms,
you can't make me,
kukla, buddy!
Sock broke my beef stick,
can't believe it,
look at this,
this thing broke
my beef stick,
which one of them is ginger,
and which one's Mary Ann?
There's only one way,
what?
We chop our way through,
yes,
ready?
After me,
Oh, wow,
he got smeared
with rustoleum,
what a time to be caught
without a turtleneck,
I don't think my socks
have ever gotten that bad,
ew,
egg rolls,
torque runs!
I'm not human,
hey, chipper‐‐ oops,
you owe me one, woman,
so, now it's two women,
I pay my debts quickly,
now back to one woman,
this whole movie is just
socks and violence,
just go away!
They did some good work for
the out‐of‐work hand models,
Hey, don't touch my hair,
I worked real hard
on that hair,
you've saved me
a second time,
now you can be his friend,
so it's two again?
I owe allegiance to no man,
‐ one,
‐ I asked no allegiance,
only your help
in leading us
to our destination,
an oasis lies ahead,
there, we can rest,
and you can get those little
cow cream pitchers,
what I need is a tune‐up,
dudes, totally
awesome job in there,
really coming together
as a group,
Look at all this water,
it's sure to rust
my micro‐circuits,
[all] Shut up,
Hey, this doesn't look
like the brochure,
there was supposed to be
a tennis court here,
what's down in there?
‐ bean fish,
‐ you don't wanna know,
looks like a lava lamp,
oh, it's the dark one,
‐‐on their way to us,
"the dark wah,"
the rebels,
they're still alive,
they must have
the immunity too,
perhaps, no matter,
it is better
they still live,
better?
Yes, we can use
the girl's life as leverage,
or end it,
she looks like
the new Lily munster,
we have nothing to fear‐‐
but fear itself,
‐‐the might of our transbots,
have you forgotten?
The warrior woman
has destroyed
a number of our best units,
perhaps it is time
to send torque,
you have made the right
decision, valaria,
then send dolenz
and nesmith too,
Has the man revealed
anything to you?
Just his hernia scar,
his will is strong,
what power have you used?
We have taken him twice,
you know, he's great, and you
never see his lips move,
seven,
he is to be reckoned with,
take him to nine,
number nine,
revive him!
I need him awake,
revive with vivarin,
how can you breathe
the poison air?
Well, I worked at a Mexican
restaurant for a while,
and then I worked
in the primate house‐‐
you leave me no choice,
torque, you are to leave
the power station
and intercept the group
that approaches us,
and, when you reach them,
the first thing
you are to do
is kill the girl,
do you understand?
Yes,
do you understand, old man?
Yeah, it's young girl
I don't understand,
‐‐your daughter
will be destroyed,
you will never
see her again,
now, do you wish
to say anything?
Yeah, do you
know Elmer Fudd?
Very well,
torque, go now,
what about Barbara Walters?
Or Truman capote?
Daffy duck?
You have signed
a death sentence
for your own daughter,
gee, I know
there's an ez‐mart
around here somewhere,
if only we could
find a city,
wait,
his wound is infected,
what can we do?
Here's someone
that can help you,
I don't think so,
no!
Greystoke, do something!
Come on, little buddy,
use the sharp edge,
hey, I knew bolos
were popular, but‐‐
oh!
He really wears it well,
damn cordless thing,
this is going
right back to the store,
swing easy,
keep your blade steady,
your eyes on the head,
Oh, it's a spare,
gutterhead,
get away, get away!
Oh man, can robots puke?
Oops,
high fly ball,
hey, there's another one,
hey, it's a Billy idol video,
they're just dancing
with theirselves,
it's a force field,
my only power as a freebot,
oh, we gotta go,
‐ hurry!
‐ let's get out of here,
let's us hurry,
Oh boy, I've got a date
with the mcguffey triplets,
they're contortionists,
the mathematic possibilities
are mind‐boggling!
[Crowd laughs]
Hey, servo,
[crowd claps]
What's up?
Got a date with the mcguffey
triplets, crow,
well, better bring
a calculator,
‐ [canned laughter]
‐ or an abacus,
why an abacus?
One of them is Chinese!
[Canned laughter]
If you're dating triplets,
you're gonna
have to go borrow
father O'Leary's Van,
oh, but he'll never
let me borrow it,
unless he thinks
we're going
to a church meeting,
[canned laughter]
Hi guys, up up and away!
[Canned laughter]
What's going on?
Oh, nothing,
[canned laughter]
Oh, really?
[Canned laughter]
‐ kind of hanging out,
‐ [canned laughter]
Uh, it sounds like cambot's
sitcom simulator is
kind of out of whack,
I'd better go check‐‐ aah!
[Canned laughter]
Oh, my knee,
[canned laughter]
‐ oh man, we‐‐
‐ Joel, this is awful,
we gotta
shut it off somehow,
oh, okay, cambot,
give us the regular picture,
better,
I guess we've learned
not to toy
with the laws of television,
[movie alarm]
Oh, we got movie sign!
There you go,
‐‐not too late to save
your daughter,
‐ she may be immune to‐‐
‐ "druder"?
‐ the poisoned air‐‐
‐ is that what she said?
‐ but she's not immune to‐‐
‐ druder?
Transbots' blaster,
does she have a big piece
of hard candy in her mouth,
‐ or something?
‐ ‐‐as is mine,
meaning what?
Deeja would rather
both of us die
than have me give in
to your demands,
do you understand
what you are saying?
Look, sister,
I don't understand
anything you've said
for the last half hour,
I'm going to put you through
the tortures of the damned,
when I'm through with you,
you will beg to tell me
what I want to know,
‐ she's very well groomed,
‐ nothing
you can do to me
will make me tell you
what you want to hear,
you're a strong man,
I will Grant you that,
no one has endured
the room of questions
for as long as you have,
she studied under
buckwheat, I guess,
oh, and what of deeja?
Supposed I have torque
bring her back
to the power station
and put her through
what you have endured?
You will first have
to catch her, won't you?
Yes, that is true,
isn't it?
Now where is that city?
Uh, queens is back there,
behind you there,
scarecrow? Tin man? Lion?
Hey, who's the guy
in the huggies?
[Narrator] Near the entrance
to the power station‐‐
‐ that depends,
‐ the rebels face,,,
‐ yet another example,,,
‐ oh, stop it,
of the dark one's cruelty,
wow, that's, uh,
biggest cardboard
cutout ever,
wow,
worst matte painting yet,
These are the winners
of the airslave battles,
Ah, I've seen chickens hurt
worse than that get better,
give me a slice of that,
oh, there's still a little
meat on there, yeah,
in this compartment
of my ring I fill
with a proton
super‐energy pill,
thank you, shoeshine,
you are humble and skeletal,
it was his father,
is she gonna be all right?
Oh, shut up, diaper man,
hey, it's Jerry Garcia,
They seem to be upset,
[all] Huh?
Do you suppose your
daughter's not as strong
as you think she is?
Deeja can take care
of herself,
and so can I,
oh, really?
If you were a twee, what kind
of twee would you be?
Perhaps it is time for you
to see what awaits you,
behold, the dark one,
it's a brand new car!
I think you'll like it,
it's got factory air
and all the candy,
neat, huh?
[Narrator] And so jorn
was finally face to face
with the being known
as the dark one,
dark one? Ravi shankar?
A being so
hideously expensive
we couldn't show it
on this film,
look, guys, a seal tank,
hey, it says,
"basement to the alamo,"
come on, guys,
single file,
don't push,
now, on your right,
you'll see
the alamo root cellar,
and, on your left,
the alamo rumpus room,
and, uh, watch
your head there,
yup, there you go, Kai,
Aren't you glad
you used dial?
Don't you wish
all subterraneans did?
You've got
underworld wetness,
‐ we're being watched,
‐ we've been watched since‐‐
of course you're being watched,
it's a film, idiot,
it's true,
it can see all,
from the power station,
then we have no chance
of taking them by surprise,
if they knew
we were coming‐‐
they'd've baked a cake,
This kind of looks
like it was filmed
in the furnace room of
a junior high or something,
hello, Cleveland!
‐ rock and roll!
‐ let's do it!
I've never been
this far before,
what lies ahead
is unknown to me,
we are in,,,
‐ what?
‐ nothing, nothing,
klyton, what were you
going to say?
It is called
"the vault of beasts,"
why?
Because the hospitality room
was already taken,
‐‐a series of traps
to ensnare those
who would try to invade
this domain,
what kind of traps?
I don't know,
my microchip board
does not contain
that information,
well, what good
are you, then?
So we're walking through
a live minefield?
I'm afraid so,
well, we can't
just stand here,
‐ let's go,
‐ well, you can just
stand there,
I mean, it's possible,
we move on,
‐ let's stay close,
‐ what are they
looking for anyway,
clothing?
Uh, Tina's looking
for a support garment,
well, I hope she
doesn't find one,
the nuge has a saggy diaper
that leaks,
in the amphitheater,
the airslaves work
to fuel the dark one's
power supply,
hey, Johnny,
you heading over
to t, j, smugglers tonight?
Are we to remain
slaves forever?
The warrior and the others
have been gone for a day,
we all know that we
will never see them again,
they are dead,
‐ what would you have‐‐
‐ so we can leave?
Each time we try to escape,
the dark one has taken away
the air we breathe,
how did rosencrantz and
guildenstern get in this film?
Korla, all of you, listen,
if we stop bringing fuel
to the power station,
the dark one will have
no power to control us,
are you mad?
If the dark one hears
of what you say,
we will all die,
korla, hear me,
listen to me, I was
in godspell once,
if the warrior and deeja
still live‐‐
hey, that guy behind him's
got his headphones on wrong,
‐ ‐‐not us,
‐ so?
So, we will all
go through the motions
of bringing fuel
to the machines,
if the powers of
the dark one monitor us,
they will see us working,
‐ and?
‐ and‐‐
isn't he wearing the shirt
that Brando wore
in streetcar named desire?
Yep,
what do you see?
A five dollar globe lamp,
they are in
the vault of beasts,
the walls of grease?
No, it's not that,
what of the airslaves?
It's not easy growing
the best potatoes in the world,
but it's worth it,
their work continues,
dark one,
good, make sure torque
attends to our visitors,
as you command,
you know, they got
a lot of heat loss
coming out of that computer,
a little caulking
would really help,
caulking?
‐ hello, Cleveland!
‐ rock and roll!
Let's do it!
Hey, crustacean‐head,
huh?
Hey, could you get my lighter
when you're down there?
Come on, you goldbricker,
get up, you're not hurt,
come on, shake it off,
wuss,
all right, folks,
back it up,
give him some air,
everybody,
come on, he's gonna be okay,
show's over,
everybody go home,
go home,
hey guys, watch
that first step,
it's a doozy,
now that's unfortunate skin
right there, guys,
he's the crawdaddy,
hey, he'd be great
with drawn butter,
or cocktail sauce,
he's a crustafarian,
you know, you serve him
with red red wine,
‐‐death, old man,
is that her tail?
No, she just played with
her stick until it frayed,
her dress looks like something
they cut gaskets out of,
his will is powerful,
valaria,
no one is a match for your
strength, dark one,
dogma?
There is only one way
for him to know,
yes?
Let him join with me,
uh, just wait until
this jet goes over, dark one,
wait till this
commercial goes over,
will it go over?
Go over great,
hello, Cleveland!
Rock and roll!
Let's do it, Cleveland!
Huh?
How did the creature die?
We are not alone
in these tunnels,
keep your weapons
at the ready,
we could be next,
not if we remain alert,
come,
aren't they
the kids from fame?
They're gonna dance forever,
we're gonna learn
how to cry,
just hope they don't get
to a lunch room,
oh, hi, crusty,
hello, ladyfish,
why would you kill one
of the inferior beings
instead of the girl?
Their path away
from the body
now leads them
to the beast of the web,
‐ a cylon wannabe,
‐ very good, torque,
your programming is more
advanced than I thought,
you think so?
I've really been
working on it,
‐‐the girl?
No, not now,
it is too late,
whatever
information we need
will come from the dark one,
‐ the dart board?
‐ he has,,,
joined with
the girl's father,
the others?
If you have led them
in the right direction,
they will no longer
be of concern to us,
[all] What?
Hey, wouldn't it be funny
if they ran into
master carpenter
norm abramson?
Uh, what we're doing here,
Bob, is, uh,
we got this little
robot problem,
they look like heart,
the rock group,
kind of,
the Wilson sisters?
‐ oh yeah,
‐ why was that mutant killed,
and why was it right
in front of us?
It was a warning,
a warning?
A sign that we should
not go any further,
uh, you got a blemish there,
it's a, uh, robo‐shanker,
the dark one,
the dark one?
‐ why?
‐ he used to play
with the Beatles,
‐ robo‐shankar?
‐ mm‐hmm,
perhaps he knows
we are immune,
not all of us,
‐ the dark one may‐‐
‐ some of us are equity,
well, I hope not, Kai's
unprotected and so am I,
well, the rest of us
are fine,
and since you are just men,
what difference does it make?
Hey, I think
someone's forgetting
who's holding the pink slip,
little lady,
‐‐excuse for a human
I have ever met,
catfight!
There's no time for this,
‐ Neo!
‐ you mean duck?
Help!
Uh, don't everybody
move at once,
what?
The beast of the web,
come!
There are only moments
to save her,
♪ the itsy‐bitsy spider ♪
♪ went up the waterspout ♪
Lancelot!
Come back, you dumkopf,
come back here!
Hey, you left your femur,
night will fall soon, roan,
I know, korla,
we must continue,
but they will soon know
at the power station
that we have not‐‐
hey, posture,
buddy, posture,
the warrior, deeja, and
the others may still live,
what good can come of that?
Well, my boss has
Bob fosse's home number,
their might could be
stronger than the dark one's,
‐ how?
‐ the dark one
draws his energy
from our labors,
if we provide him
with no energy,
they just might
have a chance,
‐ a chance?
‐ yes!
They are the only hope
we have,
please cross
behind the actors,
do you mind?
Well, that settles it,
let's go to dance class,
and ramesses said
to build a city,
my favorite food?
Cherry pez,
no question about it,
why should we
wait out the night?
We should strike now,
the morning will
be soon enough,
the power station
cannot track us by night,
all the more reason
we should attack them now,
it's deep,
they do not know
if we are even still alive,
he's right,
maybe we can
make some smores,
no, because he's right,
and besides, if we sleep
now for a few hours,
we'll be that much
more alert for
what lies ahead
in the morning,
you're hopeless,
a man tells you
what to do,
and you follow his orders
without question,
I'm following
nobody's orders,
Neo just makes
the most sense,
suit yourself,
we wake up dead in the morning,
you'll know who's to blame,
funny, we'll be dead,
what a spaz,
there's the nuge,
locked, cocked,
ready to rock,
‐ dude,
‐ dog scratch,
no‐no‐no, cat scratch!
Cat scratch!
I gotta go tell somebody,
"cat scratch fever,"
this is great!
What is it, little fella?
Snack? Gotta go walkies?
Can't believe she's sleeping
with an Android,
‐ ow,
‐ gone,
his brother
called me a coward,
he's gone out ahead,
how long ago?
Can you tell?
No,
he is headed toward
the power station,
come, we must follow,
Have you freed
the surveillance drone?
Yes, mistress,
it has been caged
for some time now,
so it should be very hungry,
go into the tunnels and‐‐
do you think they shop
at the same place
mad Max does?
I don't want it
attacking the girl,
she must get here alive,
yes, mistress,
I love it when
he calls me mistress,
Hey, I had a dream about
a big donut like that,
you know what that means,
he was hungry?
Sometimes a donut
is just a donut,
it's the wheel
of misfortune,
looks like the pirates
of the Caribbean ride
at Disneyland,
it's Rex Smith,
boy, I hate coming
to the basement alone,
not another extended
basement scene,
grandma, is it by
the peaches?
I'm kind of scared!
There's nothing there
in the dark that
isn't there in the light,
[crow groans]
I think I found
grandpa, though,
part of him,
This music can't be good,
kitty!
Bad kitty,
how long can we
continue this
before we are discovered?
We must keep on
for as long as we can,
if the dark one has found
the warrior and the others,
he would've drawn
from the power source
in order to destroy them,
since he hasn't?
Each minute
the others survive,
the power of the dark one
diminishes,
let us hope they continue
safely on their way,
and let's keep doing our
stretching exercises,
I just hope
I find some pants,
Rock and roll!
‐ let's do it!
‐ hello, Cleveland!
‐ bray!
‐ quiet,
the film was rated "b"
for basement,
That woman changes clothes
more often than
Mary Tyler Moore,
lord knows she's
got more pantsuits
than Angie Dickinson,
I'm impressed,
they shall not
come any closer,
of course, oh dark one,
I have sent torque to‐‐
if they do come
any closer, valaria,
I will be
very angry with you,
dark one, I assure you
they are all doomed,
except the girl,
of course, master,
she will be brought to you,
wow, she must've studied at
the Gabor institute
of acting and attitude,
‐‐and I will not
forget the mistake,
you have nothing to fear,
dark one,
I know!
But you do,
uh‐oh,
dark one is torqued,
meanwhile,
back in the basement,
Billy, where are you, boy?
Billy?
Hey!
[Gurgling]
Must've been
something he ate,
or something that ate him,
somebody's been
watching alien,
ooh, don't straddle
that thing,
the boy is dead,
he feels nothing,
[monster screams]
Could we get
some pepto bismol?
How about a flea collar?
That felt good,
hey, clean my sword, thanks,
ew,
Go touch the fence,
I'm not gonna touch it,
you touch it,
let's get Michelle
to touch it,
she'll touch anything,
ooh, Scooby, we gotta
get out of here!
‐‐go to your stations!
What did she say?
Was she talking to us?
‐ huh?
‐ what?
Valaria, am I to learn
that you have failed me?
No, dark one,
what, did she say
"D'Artagnan"?
‐ dork moor?
‐ dork munger?
‐‐to seed,
let this remind you
of what will be your fate,
she could've had a really good
career in silent pictures,
‐‐i swear, I will
not fail you,
‐ please,
‐ lovely,
‐ very well,
wow, you got a cigarette
there, darky‐baby?
Torque awaits at the gate,
the girl will be yours,
dark one,
I promise,
yes, she will be mine,
or what awaits you
will be far worse
than anything
you have inflicted
on any of the others,
or any of the effects,,,
‐ you've seen so far,
‐ what are we to do?
Power in the gate makes
it impossible to pass,
well, maybe try some
roughage or some bran,
wait, I know what to do,
my operational mechanisms
are energized
by the same kind
of electrical force,
I can adjust my circuitry
to achieve a matching level
of source input,
the gate's electrification
will not affect me,
aw, can the balloon
juice, sparky,
‐ just do something, will you?
‐ ‐‐metal man, get working,
Ooh,
almost got it,
ahh,
‐ great, now it's welded shut,
‐ that should do it,
I feel like a new freebot,
I will go over,
there should be a release
on the other side
to open the‐‐
malfunction reports!
I am but a freebot,
report malfunction,
freebot klyton!
A week before, that guy
was playing Hamlet,
I will go over!
Malfunction report!
That, ladies and gentlemen,
is one of the liberators
of earth,
‐ pathetic,
‐ here, let me,
malfunction report!
I am but a freebot!
Report malfunction!
Freebot klyton!
Must repair,
you know, fellas,
it's real sad
when it happens
to someone you know,
yeah, but sooner or later,
it's gonna happen
to all of us,
tell me about it,
Shouldn't they get a wallet
under his tongue or something?
‐‐going to take a while,
it's too late for that,
underoos are fun to wear,
Where do you even start
with something like that?
[Joel]
First, you cry,
uh‐huh, think you can do
a power sit‐up, little buddy?
‐ give him air,
‐ oh, hiya, crabby,
‐ hi, ladyfish,
‐ you fool!
You've let me past the gate,
do you know what you've done?
Yeah, he let them
past the gate,
the island wall
still stands
between them
and the power station,
activate the power in
all sections of the station,
what is this?
You're operating at only
one‐fourth the capacity,
must be the uh, meter,
for capacity,
dark one, no, we have
watched the airslaves
work in the amphitheater,
they proceed as always,
then, perhaps, our visitors
are responsible,
is this possible?
I don't‐‐ I will
find out at once,
yes, do that,
torque? Go to the master
monitors
and report to me the level
of energy storage
accumulated
from the airslaves,
crabby, do this,
crabby, do that,
[dark one] See, captain valaria?
The next move that you make
will be the most
important ones of your life,
career decision?
Maybe dental hygiene,
how do you feel, bucket‐head?
I can work again,
totally functional,
I am in your debt,
so what's our next move?
We'll never be able to get
through that wall without‐‐
‐ explosives?
‐ that would be helpful,
‐ allow me,
‐ oh, great,
explosive throat cancer,
no thanks,
I'm jabbing around in there,
and the whole time,
you could have gone off
at any moment?
Yet it's perfectly safe
without a detonating device,
how's it work?
Here, look,
Oh, I guess he's got like,
plenty of them in there,
into the "shaving cream
under the door" gag,
Don't just sit there,
please come on,
take cover, quick,
before the r, a, gets here,
you blew it!
[Grunting]
[Electronic warbling]
I have six, seven, eight!
[Dark one]
Your time runs short, valaria,
the guardbots
will contain them,
‐ huh?
‐ what?
‐ aah!
Hey, looks like
the set from the wiz,
[screaming]
[Screaming continues]
Spinach tin,
you go that way,
[dark one]
What is to stop them now,
valaria?
There are more guardbots,
and if they, too,
are vanquished?
[Tom servo]
Even more guardbots,
there is one final obstacle
they are about to encounter,
[servo]
The windmill,
now,
boy, oh boy, if I weren't
a light fixture, ooh!
It's ze wango ze tango!
‐ you got your maserati‐‐
‐ huh?
It's a bomb, rigged to go off
with any further‐‐
yeah, it is a bomb,
maybe you should have
made a different film,
clear the way
for the rest of us,
thanks,
i, uh, needed that,
there may be
some hope for you yet,
as a gorgeous
lady of wrestling,
all right,
now what do we do?
I've seen these devices before,
at the edge of the wasteland,
‐ leading into the last city,
‐ my aunt's got one,
listen to me carefully, Kai,
‐ can you hear me?
‐ [coughs] Nuh‐uh,
from where I stand,
I can't see what you can,
there should be a steel cylinder
in front of you, near your head,
is there?
If that thing goes off,
he'll be playing Vincent,
is there a small knob
at the tip of one end?
‐ no knob!
‐ slowly, move your hand
up to the bomb
without touching the wires
at your side,
but, before you do that‐‐
have you got it?
Now, reach into
your left breast pocket,
the knob
is a trigger mechanism,
it is attached to the explosives
on the inside
by a very short wire,
klyton, do you have cutters
in your tool panel?
That's a little personal,
isn't it?
Are martinis good for you
guys? Everybody interested?
Carefully, unscrew the knob
on the cylinder,
when it's loose,
don't pull it away,
‐ do you understand?
‐ [clicks]
‐ and don't breathe,
‐ is it loose?
I'm reaching behind you
with the cutters,
when I'm done with this, you
will guard my harem, understand?
‐ don't clip your nails,
‐ are the cutters
near the cylinder?
Cut, slowly,
pull the knob
away from the cylinder,
just enough to put the cutters
between the knob
and the head of the bomb,
cut the wire,
now,
boink!
Uh, I haven't cut it yet,
I'm just kidding,
thanks for playing,
valaria,
valaria, your pizza's here,
‐ what is it?
‐ the energy reservoir
from the amphitheater‐‐
that guy needs a kleenex,
real bad,
what? But
we saw them working,
‐ [dark one]
What did you see, valaria?
‐ the airslaves,
airslaves, they're
a beast of burden,
and they somehow
got the best of you,
valaria, what can
I do with you?
Don't worry, please!
Torque, take her away
from my sight!
No, dark one, please!
Taking someone out of
an omnipresent being's sight
is pretty tough to do,
when you think about it,
very well,
I will bring the gold
to you myself,
and she will tell you
what you want to know,
‐ [clears throat]
‐ [dark one]
One last chance, valaria,
and then you know
the fate that awaits you,
‐ thank you, dark one,
you will not be sorry,
‐ diction school,
oh, pulsating glass ball
with hair like Sam donaldson,
please tell me what to do‐‐
we better get out of here,
‐ carry me?
‐ no, ow,
do it, summon the guardbots,
It was after the apocalypse,
it was after the robots
had taken over the earth,
there stood a lone,
desperate survivor,
in a dark, dangerous time,
crow the hunter,
and his animal boy, geekor,
a lonely human, dressed
in the skins of those
lesser on the food chain,
but not by much,
the boldest of them all
was servo the bloodletter,
servo, the chirping
hell‐beast,
servo, the defiler
of all that is‐‐
oh, yeah, okay,
so the lonely Tom strode forth
in a search for the pathetic
terror awaiting them
in the dark,
evil power quadrant,
ah, hey, could we stop
at a Wendy's first, guys?
Geekor here wants a frosty
in a bad way,
silence, beaked fool,
you dare to mock the power
of the dark one?
‐ the block plan?
‐ black one?
What? The dark one!
The dark one!
‐ oh‐h, dark one,
‐ oh,
uh, listen, you know Tom, sir,
I'm not getting too into this,
I feel kind of like
king vitamin
miscast in a Sonny
and Cher video,
and besides, are these
real furs or what?
Yeah, what are we wearin',
road kill here?
I mean, hey, these‐‐
these furs are either
cruel or unsanitary,
depending on your point of view,
well, it's after
the apocalypse and everything,
and well, we got the furs
from the dead animals
littering the countryside,
ah, road kill!
See, I told you, Joel!
‐ we're wearing road kill,
‐ oh, that's just great,
Tom servo's having
some kind of
right‐wing conservative
fur party, and I think
we should just leave him, crow,
let's let mr, narcissist
alone here,
so he can have his own
party of access,
‐ let's get outta here,
‐ yeah, see you at
the seal‐clubbing meeting,
‐ not!
‐ oh!
‐ [whistles tunelessly]
‐ [narrator] He stood proudly,
the bold survivor
of the weak and unwilling race,
we're among friends, aren't we?
Tell me your deep, dark
secrets, my little furry friend?
We'll rule the countryside,
and we'll be one together,
‐ okay,
‐ it's your planet,
I don't want you
wearing this hat anymore,
‐ hey,
‐ hey, that guy had a tough day,
he was off to Murray's
for a schmitty,
Ever seen this one?
I can walk the dog, too,
Boy, if I could fight
like those robots‐‐
boy, this is what I'd do,
get me some swords and
they wouldn't stand
a chance against me,
now, how much would
you pay for this robot?
Wait! Stop!
There's more,
it slices, it dices,
it makes a great julienne fry,
hey, not bad
for a crustacean,
sure, I got my pants glued,
maybe I should have brought
an oyster knife,
Let me escape‐‐
hurry, i‐‐
‐ oh!
‐ in the future, all robots
will act like Don knotts,
‐ hey!
‐ oh, no!
I saw Darth Vader
do that once,
ah‐uh‐uh‐uh‐‐
you got it,
catfight,
Ugh, right in the throat,
see, dark one?
I kept my promise,
the girl is yours,
[dark one] You are as good
as your word, valarian,
but your use to me
has still come to an end,
but dark one, I delivered
on my promise,
life isn't always fair,
valaria, especially when‐‐
oh, always get a contract
when you're dealing with
a dark, omnipotent power,
gotta be read,
girl, if we ever
get like these bots,
would you please shut us down?
Like, just take us out,
she shouldn't be by that
Worthington machine, you know?
Those things are known to, uh,
have a problem with their‐‐
agh, yeah,
she wasn't wearing
her safety goggles!
‐ it's a problem,
‐ should have expected it,
[screaming]
‐ she likes it!
‐ dark one, can you hear me?
Yes, valarian, what do you
wish to say before you die?
In spite of what you say,
I was never really alive,
so what matters it to me
what becomes of me,
or all of us?
She sounds kind of like
an obsession commercial,
‐ set a distraction‐‐
‐ ♪ [music]
Hey, don't turn that up,
power company says 68, tops!
Ah, the fries are up,
in five minutes,
all of you who remain
will be destroyed,
the blast to her face
kind of helped her diction,
and you, and all the others
will cease to exist!
Well, good, as long as we don't
"cease" to "exist",
or what?
You will destroy me?
It doesn't matter anymore,
nothing does!
I don't know
what's gotten into her,
she just doesn't sound like
the malaria I used to know,
ah, he's‐‐ whoa!
Oh, it's the huge nuge,
That's for r2 d2,
that's for c3po,
that's for julie‐‐ newmar‐‐
and that's just 'cause
I wanna!
What have I done?
Oh, man, the huge nuge,
he's got cat scratch fever,
right on his chest,
No! No!
Would somebody get
those fries, please?
‐ where is my father?
‐ which father?
That could be anyone,
[dark one]
He is,,, nearby,
take me to him,
tell me what
I want to know,
okay, well, you're kind of cute,
you're kind of pretty,
but you have a big cartoon
when I hold you in my arms,
I never know what to do,
[dark one]
Some of your friends are
immune to my powers, why?
I don't know,
are you? And you will
tell me, now!
You know, I kind of miss
her two guys,
‐ I can see why,
‐ yeah, all that equipment,
yeah, it's neat,
[generator whining]
Go ahead, waste your
stupid energies on each other,
‐ it's eartha kitt!
‐ what will it matter,
in less than a minute,
the entire power station
will be destroyed,
‐ what have you done?
‐ what hasn't she done?
What do you think?
You're finished,
so's the dark one,
torque, then the activation
lies under the far wall‐‐
ooh,
‐ [grunting]
‐ hey, don't touch
the threads, man,
it's hot on the fringe,
[Electrical whining]
It's kind of like
a solid gold dance routine,
torque, come to the room,,,
at once!
Come on,
valaria, I thought
we had seen the last of you,
dark one, forgive me,
I'm here to serve you,
‐ please believe me,
‐ I got no problem with that,
is that why you activated
the mechanism
that could have
destroyed us all?
But I could save us all,
our power is depleted,
and it is because
of the traitors
in the work yards
of the amphitheater,
I can't even guess
what she's saying,
,,,the earth's lift,
to begin with fueling,,,
come on, edsel‐head, speak up!
,,,and regain our dominance
over them,
‐ [dark one] How?
‐ the girl will tell us,
‐ never,
‐ why should she?
When she sees what's become
of her father,
and what will become of her,
‐ fur?
‐ did she say "fur"?
‐ what will become of "fur"?
Hey, my card opened this teller,
and I don't even bank here!
[Chuckles]
Go figure,
I'm all aquiver
with anticipation,
‐ what the‐‐
‐ all that remained of jorn
was his head,
the rest of his body
was completely engulfed,
‐ by the dark one,
‐ [guffawing]
He looks like something
from one fish, two fish,
I am the egg man!
Dad, you're a tulip bulb,
well, at least we know
what mclean Stevenson's
been doing since mash,
honey, remember my torso?
Well, it's chip dip now,
hello, Larry,
the dark one has
consumed your father,
with all his strength
and wisdom,
when your jorn was the only one,
no longer will lead‐‐
hey, you don't have
to draw me a picture, okay,
my dad belongs
in a salad bar,
bet the inside of his suit
smells like a mushroom farm
at this point,
well, the nice thing is,
her dad can fly as carry‐on,
‐ or carrion,
‐ hey, get me, I'm an appetizer!
I'm giving out spores!
I've been wearing this
ridiculous costume for hours,
I'm cramping
like Kathy rigby,
‐ ooh!
‐ stop playing with your food,
please don't jump on me
right now,
I'm feeling
kind of vulnerable,
Yeah! Crusty's been watching
old episodes of mannix,
run away!
‐ she's drunk with power,
‐ and she's drunk with makeup,
nah, she's just got
her beer goggles on,
and now, it is time
to show the airslaves
what their treachery
has earned them,
we no longer need them,
with the knowledge of jorn
and his daughter,
we can power the station
from within,
the time has come
for all of them‐‐
oh, wait,
I'm on daylight savings,
what am I doing?
We have an hour to go,
[Coughing]
Ah, they must have unzipped
that avocado suit,
stay in character, everyone,
try to stay on camera,
aw, she's stoned,
‐ oh, this tool,
‐ not again!
Come on!
[Screaming]
Guess it worked
at the last minute,
as you are
when you want to return them,
Ah, look at me, I'm trying
to have a fight,
and I got Peter Pan here,
hopping around,
uh‐oh, he's gonna use
the wrapping paper tube,
that's for putting lemon
and drawn butter on my head!
That guy's been the sand
in my shell long enough,
Let's see,,,
the human goes,,,
through the hole,
around the tank,
and uh, hmm,
there he is,
first look up!
Ohh,
lights are on,
but nobody's home,
that's for mrs, Paul!
That's for gorton's
of gloucester,
that's for Arthur treacher,
that's for Abe Saul,
that's for filet‐o‐fish,
good pose with the filet,
if they put him together
with the avocado man,
they'd make
a great seafood plate,
if you see me now,
I'm as good as dead,
okay, okay, honey,
am I a fruit or a vegetable,
I can't! I love you!
‐ you love me,
‐ he's "Jack the beanstalk,"
they say it's the only way
out of here,
father, please,
you know, I was gonna help you
take on that big, robotic guy,
but you seemed to be doing
pretty good by yourself, so‐‐
here, take my robotic truss,
You know, underneath all
this block is a heart of gold,
you know what to do,
know who you are,
flee that olden terror!
Yes! Don't do it!
Don't do it!
‐ they've got the pitch!
‐ [screams]
Ooh, stir‐fry!
This is what it sounds like
when bulbs cry,
thank you, Neo,
for killing my dad,
the airslaves!
[Compressor starting,
air rushing]
Ah, it's amazing
what you can do,
just by turning on
an egg‐timer,
kind of reminds me of
an acting class I used to have,
Freedom! Freedom!
The dark one is dead,
avocado man is dead,
this looks like the locker room
for American gladiator,
‐ smells like it!
‐ mm‐hmm,
looks like the closing night
cast party of that's dancing!
They're really well‐groomed for
being at the end of the world,
deeja, jorn would have
wanted it this way,
he wanted to be laid
to rest on a hill, and,,,
‐ no,
‐ not scooped out
for a light lunch,
‐ Neo,
‐ what will you do now?
Go back to my people,
finish my father's work,
‐ try to find a better script,
‐ no, leave me alone!
Maybe,,, learn how to act,
your father was a great man,
and an even better side dish,
a lot better dead than a spread,
what a dick,
[Laughing]
My dad's his own
favorite dish,
‐ and she's my favorite dish,
‐ hey!
You could still
get a job at chi‐chi's,
you could be the job,
[Narrator] With the dark one
destroyed‐‐
[together]
Oh! The dark one!
[Narrator]
Neo returned to his people,
to bring them to the last city,
together,
they would
rebuild new terra,
so it would be
"newer terra," then,
"newest terra,"
if not, they might get
their waiter jobs back,
or do odd jobs for their
cousin's house‐building company,
probably got enough investors
for a new sequel, yeah,
oh, man, let's pray
it's not a buddy picture,
he's a robot, he's a human,
they're detectives!
[Laughing]
‐ hey, let's not have that,
‐ well, what?
‐ you do it bad,
‐ what did you think
of the movie, guys?
‐ do you really want to know?
‐ yeah,
I think it gave
robots a bad name,
I really got upset
by that metallic pantywaist,
the robot‐‐ he really
got under my skin,
yeah, I liked seeing, uh,
nugent, though, you know,
spread his wings
and try some new things,
‐ yeah,
‐ it's nice to see
he was working, and‐‐
did you know he's
George Clinton's neighbor?
‐ who's George Clinton?
‐ oh, he's this guy on earth,,,
funkadelic?
He invented funkadelic,
so it's a rockin'
neighborhood, then,
"brides of funkenstein,"
‐ they're throwing
a block party,
‐ sure,
‐ whoo!
‐ a rockin' block party,
‐ police have been called,
‐ yes,
‐ I don't know,
‐ one thing we gotta do
is get a contest
‐ to name that avocado guy?
‐ oh, good idea,
‐ have him, uh‐‐
‐ the color thing was nice,
‐ the color thing?
‐ the fact that this movie
was in color,
oh, yeah, I mean, instead
of looking at a black,
we're looking
at kind of a burgundy,
‐ much better,
‐ yeah,
I like it a lot,
‐ you want to get going?
‐ yeah, let's uh‐‐
no, I want to see
the key grip,
‐ oh,,,
‐ hey, look at this,
"special visual effects
created
by Jeremy frank for
bizarrchitecture,"
look, mr, French, I didn't know
his first name was ed,
"James chai,"
‐ chairman mao's anagram,
‐ he's, like, eating chow,
hey, Joel, did you ever
look at the floor in here?
‐ yuck!
‐ it's really a mess,
now that I think about it,
we should have cam‐‐
actually,
I should get back
to fixing cambot,
‐ let's go,
‐ all right,
‐ carry me,
‐ oh‐ho?
Oh, come on!
Oh, I'm not gonna‐‐
okay, I'll come back
for you,
your hands are like
the dark one's, Joel,
‐ all right,
‐ not carrying me, are you?
Come on, let's go,
come on, strap your
limbs around, okay,
‐ let's go,
‐ hey, Joel? You gotta come
lift me over this heating grid,
Okay, you guys, it's finally
the end of the experiment,
and um, let's have another
look at that plant guy again,
cambot, you want to fish out
that frame 5236‐‐
there he is,
up there, guys,
whoa, you know, even though
he looks scary, Joel,
I still get a little hungry,
just lookin' at him,
so, we've decided this guy
is too good
to keep to ourselves,
so, we're gonna sponsor
a "name the plant guy"
brainstorm,
right, it's a brainstorm,
everybody, so join in,
send in your name
for the plant guy,
and the top 13 will be read
on mystery science theater,
on satellite eleven,
send your plant guy
brainstorm entries to:
We've come up with
a few starters of our own,
to help you, uh,
name the plant guy,
uh, number one,
[Joel]
Our guy number two, mine is,,,
and number three: Carl,
so, well, that finishes up
this week's experiment‐‐
what do you think?
‐ what about the letter?
‐ oh, oh‐‐ oh, yeah,
got it right here,
this is from a father‐son team,
first is from Donny,
he writes, he's the dad,
"my son and myself would like
"to join the mst3k fan club,
"that scares the hell out of me,
because he's only seven,
and I'm 36,"
and later on, we've got some
from bill, the son, who says,
"hello, Joel, I'd like
to tell crow
‐ "that he's funny,
‐ hey,
"and that I like the part
when he said,
"'he's out of bang‐bang,'"
I don't really remember that,
maybe he ought to get off
the sugar cereals,
yeah! "And Joel, I'd like
to tell you,,,
"that when all said,
'nice tag,'
"and Tommy is
"'bubble‐gum head
without a slot‐‐'
oh, and thanking again
for him on three‐‐
‐ one, two, three,
‐ "nice tag,"
"p,s,, all of you are funny,"
thank you, bill and Donny,
‐ thank you, bill and Donny,
‐ how's that, sirs?
Good job, mr, memory,
I think you should
file this, Larry,
until next time,
skippy‐drawers!
♪ [Theme]